{
    "subject": "resource/Juan_Jos\u00e9_Esparragoza_Moreno",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Sinaloa",
    "human_readable": "Juan Jos\u00e9 Esparragoza Moreno was born in Sinaloa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9544419050216675,
            "question": "Where was Juan Jos\u00e9 Esparragoza Moreno born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3805873990058899,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Sinaloa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.376130074262619,
            "question": "What is Sinaloa known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2911352515220642,
            "question": "What is the history of Sinaloa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27624034881591797,
            "question": "What is the population of Sinaloa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24147598445415497,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Sinaloa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22249561548233032,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Sinaloa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20777590572834015,
            "question": "What is the main language spoken in Sinaloa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18576067686080933,
            "question": "What are some traditional dishes from Sinaloa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09079235047101974,
            "question": "What industries are important to Sinaloa's economy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Juan Jos\u00e9 Esparragoza Moreno was born in Sinaloa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8234_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some traditional dishes from Sinaloa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8234_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main language spoken in Sinaloa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8234_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Sinaloa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8234_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8234_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to the documents, Juan Jos\u00e9 Esparragoza Moreno was indeed born in Badiraguato, Sinaloa, Mexico (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8234/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt and /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8234/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Juan Jos\u00e9 Esparragoza Moreno was born in Sinaloa.\" Specifically, the documents mention that he was born in Huixiopa, Badiraguato, Sinaloa, Mexico."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}